NATALIA SOWA

Web Development Student

ABOUT ME

After 4 years working in Marketing field, I've decided to switch paths and pursue my programing dreams. I've started my journey with HackYourFuture school in Copenhagen where I got to learn how to create beneficial web solutions using various technologies, such as reactJS, mysql, expressJS etc. I'm mostly passionate about the frontend development as well as design.

WORKING EXPERIENCE

HackYourFuture Graduation Project | Link

Jan 2022 - Present - 2 months, Copenhagen

Technologies: React JS, Node JS, Storybook, Swagger, FireBase, Github.

Demant, Commercial Excellence

Assistant to Manager

Jan 2020 - Dec 2021 - 1 yr 7 mos, Smørum

Hosting of Sales Training Webinars in ISpringLearn. Implementation of the Learning & Knowledge Platform - 'Fuse' with technologies such as Figma, CSS, HTML, JS.

Oticon Medical, Marketing & Communication

Student Assistant

Aug 2018 - feb 2021 - 2 yr 7 mos, Smørum

Working with the Marketing Portal (SharePoint). Re-invoicing bi-yearly of translation costs. Assisting with the implementation and launch of a new Digital Asset Management System (DAM).

EDUCATION

HackYourFuture, Web Development | Curriculum

7-month coding bootcamp with modules on HTML, CSS, JavaScript, NodeJS, ExpressJS, MySQL and ReactJS.

2021 - 2022, Copenhagen

Aarhus BSS, Bachelor in Economics & Business Administration

2018 - 2021, Aarhus

Copenhagen Business Academy, AP in Marketing

2016 - 2018, Copenhagen

Contact

natalia.m.sowa@gmail.com

+45 91458461

O Denmark

in Linkedin/Natalia Sowa

GitHub/nataliasowa

Industry Knowledge

Website Design
Web Development
Benchmarking

Tools

GitHub,

Visual Studio Code,

CodePen,

Storybook,

Sass,

NPM

JQuery,

MySQL,

FireBase,

Figma

Technology

ExpressJs,

ReactJs,

Languages

Polish (native)

English (Professional Working

Proficiency)

Danish (basics)